Look, whenever you need money, you'll go
somewhere and apply for a loan. It's
possible that if you
apply for a loan through an application,
you might be offered a lower loan amount, a
shorter tenure, or a higher interest rate. It's
better to
try a different bank. The bank I'm going to
talk about today isn't a small bank; it's a
very large, trusted bank called
III Bank.
You can easily apply for a loan from this bank.
However, you'll know very well that
when applying for a loan from a bank, the
eligibility requirements are very strict.
However,
I'll explain the eligibility criteria to you so you
know everything in advance so you do
n't face any negative or unnecessary inquiries.
You can apply for a loan here.
I'll also explain the
complete process for applying for a loan
so you don't have any hassles.  There should be
no problem and the most interesting thing is
that you can apply for this loan sitting at home, for this
you will not need to visit any bank, see
if you apply for a loan from any bank, the
most interesting thing is that
you get to see a lot of time and loan amount here,
currently if you are going to apply for a loan from III Bank,
then you
get a loan from ₹ 5000000 to ₹ lakh here
and when you take this loan, the
timing given to you here, that is, the
turner time given, is
for a maximum of 72 months,
if I talk about the rate of interest, then the
starting rate of interest here
starts from around 10.5, although it
depends on your profile, you will get
to see it at 11, 12, 13, 14 or whatever
and here you have to keep one more thing in mind
if you are going to apply for this loan
You must keep in mind your age eligibility. If you are
between 23 and 58 years of age, then you are
eligible for this loan. However,
if you have this question in your mind:
how much should my salary be, or
what is the fuss about income proof? Then
understand this: if any bank gives you a loan, then
you have all the proofs. Based on that, they
give you cheaper loans,
longer loans, and for a longer period.
However, many such applications
come which do not look at your eligibility
and give you a loan, but what they do is they give
double the money, less time, and charge
more interest. However, the
bank works properly, that is why
you get to see everything properly here.
I am
telling you the eligibility in advance so that it becomes easier for
you to decide whether you are eligible or not.
After that, you will be
able to apply for a loan here. If I ask
you about income proof or
salary here,  If I talk about salary, then you should
understand that your
monthly income should be ₹0000 per month
and your salary of ₹5000000 should be
credited to your bank account in the statement. It is not like that, you
said brother, ₹0000 I get salary
but if I get it in cash, that will not be accepted.
If you say brother, I get it by cheque,
that too will not be accepted. If it is
transferred to your account, then it will be
shown in your statement. Brother, you
work in this company. Your salary gets credited from that company,
then it will be
very easy for you to take a loan here.
Now, a question will also arise here that
brother, what should be our CIBIL score?
If we are going to apply for a loan here, it is
possible that my loan requirement here may be
in several lakhs, that is, it can be up to 20, 30 lakh,
40 lakh. So, how much should my CIBIL be for this? I will
not say that the CIBIL is not very high, brother, it should be 800,
850.  But your civil should
be 750. If your civil is 750, then if you
apply for this loan, then there are
chances of getting a higher loan amount.
All these things
might be a bit difficult for you to hear, brother, that my
salary is so much, anything like that. So you
must understand one thing here that
if you want to take a loan of a large amount here, then
you must have at least this much
document or eligibility. That is
why I have clarified all the things for you first
so that you do not feel that
if I had known the eligibility earlier, then
I would not have applied for the loan here,
so that there is no inquiry in my civil.
Now your eligibility has been
completed here, so let us see once, by
following which steps
you will be able to apply for the loan here.
See, to apply for the loan,
I have put a link in the description.
As soon as you click on it, you will come to this page.
After coming here, first of all you have to
tell that brother, how much loan amount do you want?  You
need an amount of Rs. 5000000 to Rs.
50 lakhs.
You
can enter your desired amount here. Apart from this, you can also choose for
how long you want to take this loan.
After this, you will go to the next page.
Here you have to enter your mobile number.
After this, you have to enter your PAN
card number and the
date of birth given in your PAN card. You will
enter that date of birth. A
box of term condition will be shown here. Click on that box.
After this,
an OTP will come on your mobile number. Enter the OTP here and
click on submit. After this, on the
next page, you have to enter your Aadhar
card number so that
your KYC can be completed using your Aadhar card number.
Click on send OTP.
An OTP will come on your mobile number. Enter the OTP and
enter it here. On this page,
enter your name as given in your PAN card. On the
next page, you will see a
cancellation message here in which  It is
said that you are eligible for the loan amount
and are eligible for this much time,
but here you must keep one thing in mind
that brother, whatever loan amount is shown to you here, it
can increase or decrease in future, there is maximum
chance that it will increase, it will be more, that is why
when you verify your account,
verify your income, then the
loan amount can be shown to you here more,
then according to you you
can increase or decrease it, how will this happen, let
me show you on the next page,
after this your next page will come out,
here you have to enter your financial details, in
which first of all you have to
select whether you are a salaried person or you are
self-employed here or you do business,
whatever you do, you can select yourself here,
after this you have to
enter the name of your company here,
enter an email ID of your office,
click on verify and verify the email ID of your office,
after this you will
see, if you come down then you will see here  You will get
to see two types of options,
see if you have a salary account then
log in by entering your user ID, password etc. here, if you do not have a salary
account then what to do in that case
you will click on account aggregator here,
enter your mobile number,
you have to select your account aggregator here,
then you will be shown here
in which bank you have an account, you will get
to see all this, simply
you have to click on pay here, now
after coming here you have to verify your account
so that it can be verified,
this is your account and your account
is activated, along with this your salary
comes here, your salary can also be verified
here, what to do for this,
first of all you have to select your bank,
after this you will see which bank is yours,
enter the registered mobile number here, enter the ATM PIN card,
through this you will be able to verify it,
after this as soon as your income is verified here,
you will look at the next page, you will be
shown the loan amount which is higher here  It is
possible that in the present case,
brother, a maximum loan of ₹1150,000 can be given.
However, if your need is less, then the
minimum can be reduced to ₹5000000 or as
much as you need.
Talking about the timing, the maximum
time shown here is up to 72 months.
Brother, you
can take this loan for a maximum of 72 months. So,
you must have seen here that when your income is verified, it becomes
clear that brother, your
income is so much that you can repay the money here on time.
Your civil is also good, on
that basis, the loan amount may be
shown to you as quite high.
Depending on someone's eligibility, the
loan amount can be shown to you as less or
more. Here
you will see the loan details
in which you will get to see the loan amount, tuner
time, processing fee, interest, etc.
If your civil
is good and you have income proof, then
you will get to see the rate here.  Of interest can
also be seen on 1112, after this
you will see at the bottom how much net amount you will have to pay,
you will be
able to see all that here, after this as you go to the next page
you will need to fill up your additional details here, in
which first of all
you have to tell that your date of
birth means where you were born,
what is the name of your place, you will
enter it here, what is the purpose of taking the loan,
you will select it here,
after this select your region here,
select the category,
in marital status you will select whether you are married or
unmarried, whatever you feel is right,
you will fill it up here accordingly,
after this as you go to the next page
you will
also need to upload all your documents here, in which the first thing will be
that
you have to select brother current
employment type, suppose if I am
working somewhere then I have to prove this, whatever
I get, my employment ID etc.
or I card,
I will enter it here  I will upload it and secondly, the
verification of the office address, for example, suppose
if I am uploading the employment ID
or letter head or whatever I add, there will be the
company address in it, I will
upload that too here, after this I
also have to upload my education qualification, that is, what is
my higher education qualification,
whatever it is, I will upload it here,
after this I will simply click on continue,
after this you will see on the next page that
you will need to enable it,
enable it means that if you are
receiving money in your account, which
will be debited to you every month,
for automatic debit from your account, you have to
give permission here, you can do this work in two
ways, if you have net
banking then you can do it through net banking,
secondly, if you have a debit card then you
can complete the process by entering your details here through your debit card, after this as soon as you
click on the next page, you are told here
that brother, you will have to sign a consent agreement or you
can say that you will have to sign an agreement for this loan.  You will get
to see a place where
you will get to see a lot of information about this loan,
you
can read it, after this you will see that you have to
click on the box given here and click on sign agreement,
what will happen here is that
your agreement gets signed
so that your loan can be dispersed here, to
complete this signing, you are given an
option here in which you will
enter your Aadhar card number,
an OTP will come on your mobile number, after entering the OTP you will
click on submit, in this way
your e-sign process will be completed,
after this you have to
complete your KYC on the next page, for which
you should have a regional PAN card, a blank paper,
pen etc. and your internet
connectivity should be good, if
all this is fine then you will
complete the KYC here, as soon as the KYC is
completed, you will be
shown the cancellation message here and the
application number will be given here, the loan
amount will be shown and
through this application you can make your  You
can also track this loan, so in this way you
can apply for this loan while sitting at home.
If you have all the documents
and ability of this type, then you will be able to take this loan easily,
about which I have
shared all the information with you in this video.
For now,
I have put the link to apply for this loan in the description,
you can check it out. For now, if you have any query
related to this video,
please do let me
know by commenting and I am also sharing an email ID of
mine. If you have
any query regarding the recording of this loan, then you
can also ask by mailing on that address. For now, like this video and
subscribe to the channel. If you have
any doubt, please do let me know by commenting.
Let's meet again in the next video. Till then,
Jai Hind, Jai Bharat.